TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
그렇게, 돌격! 아이들 쇼, 여름방학 특별 기획! 시청자 여러분이 직접 등장!
Now, we're doing a special project on Charge! Children's Show! Audience's Participation!
오늘의 시청자 님은 준바이 마을의 야구 소년, 오기 니시키 군이었습니다!
Today, a baseball boy from Junbai village is here! His name was Oni Nishiki!
그라치에, 고마워요, 오니 니시키 군! 그럼 내일의 게스트 선택! 시라유키 씨, 부탁드려요!
Grazie, thank you, Oni Nishiki! Now, time for tomorrow's guest lottery! Do it, Shirayuki!
네, 네! 그럼 여름방학의 추억으로 TV에 출연!
Yes, yes! Someone's going to have a memory of appearing on the TV in summer vacation!
다음의 행운의 친구는 누굴까요?
Who will be our next lucky friend?
부탁이야! 붙어! 붙어 줘!
Please! Let me win! Let me win!
너 엽서 냈냐?
Did you submit a postcard?
이히, 시라유키 보고 싶어서 말야!
Heh, I wanted to see Shirayuki!
그래서, 그렇게 쉽게 붙는 게 아니야, 잇키.
But still, you won't be picked that easily, Ikki.
뭐, 기대하지 않는 게 충격이 적으니까 낫다는 거지.
Well, I'm saying that giving it up already would give you lesser shock, which is better.
그래, 너 어른이다.
Yeah, you're a grown-up.
오, 이건 대단한 사람이 찍혔군요!
We got an awesome person!
무슨, 로보틀 세계 대회 준우승자, 텐료 잇키 군이 당첨되었습니다!
We got Tenryo Ikki, the second place winner in the World Robattle Championship!
뭐라고!?
What!?
기쁘네요! 캔디, 메타비를 몰래 좋아하고 있었어요!
How happy it is! I, Candy, loved Metabee for a while!
그럼 잇키 군, 내일 메타비하고 둘이서 출연 부탁해요!
Then, Ikki, don't forget to come join us tomorrow with Metabee!
아, 붙었다, 붙었다! 정말 붙었어!
I got picked! I got picked! I actually got chosen!
잘했다, 잇키!
Great job, Ikki!
-어?
-사실은 나, 캔디 팬이야.
-What?
-To tell you the truth, I'm Candy's fan.
풀에서 로보틀!
Robattle in Pool!
(en: Lights, Camera... Robattle!)
대단하잖아! 그 돌격 아이들 쇼에 출연하다니!
Isn't that awesome?! You're appearing in Charge! Children's Show!
아니, 내가 당첨운이 좋으니까!
Well, you know, my luck in lotteries is good!
운도 실력의 하나니까!
Luck is a part of abilities!
물론 취재도 할게. 돌격 아이들 쇼 무대 뒤 모든 것을 보여주다! 라고.
I'll make a news story out of it, too, like, "You'll see everything behind the scenes!"
오, 뭐라도 보여주겠어!
We'll show them everything!
덤벼라!
Let it come!
나가서 바보짓이나 하지 마. 너희들의 수치는 전국의 메다로터의 수치나 다름없으니까.
Just don't act like an idiot on TV. Your disgrace is same with the disgrace to all the Medarotters in the whole country.
세계 대회 제 2의 자존심을 잊지 마!
Do not forget the pride of the 2nd in the world championship!
괜찮아, 괜찮아!
It's okay, it's alright!
참 경박하다니까. 왠지 걱정돼.
You are so fickle. I'm really worried about you guys.
어이, 잇키! 너 나간다며? 돌격 아이들 쇼에 나간다며?!
Hey, Ikki! You're appearing on Charge! Children's Show?
좋겠다, 캔디하고 시라유키하고 만나서!
Good for you! You're meet Candy and Shirayuki!
부러워!
I envy you!
그, 그래? 이야, 곤란하네.
Y- you think so? Well, that's great!
더 말해, 말해!
Say more! More!
자, 미리 협의해 둘까.
Let's talk about this for now.
어? 뭔?
About what?
당연하잖아? 텐료 잇키를 키운 라이벌 미소녀 메다로터, 키쿠히메 님의 우정 출연이지.
Isn't it obvious? The rival Medarotter who made Tenryo Ikki of now, Kikuhime, should be there, too!
말하고도 헛되지 않아요, 두목?
Don't you think that's in vain even for you, boss?
뭐라고?!
What?!
돌격 아이들 쇼야? 분명 전국 네트워크의 인기 방송이네.
Charge! Children's Show, eh? It really is a popular show on the nationwide network.
그런 엉터리 메다로터가 TV에 나오다니 마음에 안 들어! 못 나가게 지금 바로 쳐부수러 가자!
I can't let a sham Medarotter like that go on a TV! Let's go destroy them so that they won't!
잠깐. 기껏 TV에 중계잖아. 데스 메다로트의 강함을 전국에 보여줄 절호의 기회 아니야?
Wait. Aren't they going on TV once in a while?
Isn't it a good chance for us to show the power of Death Medarots to the whole country?
어, 그래?
Oh, I guess so.
성공하면 최고급 파트를 줄 건데, 어때?
I'll give you the best parts available if you succeed. What do you think?
좋은 생각이야. 그대로 할게, 코쿠류! 내일이 기대되네.
Good idea. I'll do so, Kokuryu! I'm looking forwards for tomorrow.
우라가스미, 드라곤나 준비해 줘.
Uragasumi, prepare Dragonnar.
알겠습니다, 도련님.
Understood, young master.
그래서 내일 뭐 할 거야?
So, what are you going to do tomorrow?
좋은 아침!
Mornin'!
돌격 아이들 쇼! 여름방학 특별 기획! 시청자 직접 등장! 오늘은 음양 마을 야외 수영장에 나와 있습니다!
Charge! Children's Show special project! We let a guest join! Today, we're out at the outdoor pool of Ginjou village!
이른 아침부터 수영장이라니, 이 방송 대체 무슨 생각이야?
What were they thinking, to be here at a pool from early morning?
좋아.
Well.
그래서 오늘은 로보틀 세계 대회 준우승자, 텐료 잇키 군입니다!
Today, we have Tenryo Ikki, the semi-finals winner of Robattle World Championship!
뭐야, 저 칠칠맞은 얼굴은?
What's wrong with their slovenly face?
바람직해! 잇키 놈, 정말 바람직해!
What an excellent face! Ikki's looking great!
가만히 보고 있지만 마! 뭔가 한번에 비위 맞추어서 TV에 나가!
Don't stay silent! Do whatever to make them let us appear on TV!
안 돼, 안 돼!
No, no!
아, 그게, 저는 잇키와 고락을 함께한 친구로...
Well, that's, I'm a friend with Ikki who shared joys and sorrows!
방해방해.
You're interefering.
두목, 꼴사나워요.
Boss, you're unsightly.
그럼 물어 보겠습니다. 잇키 군의 강함의 비밀은?
Then, let us ask right away. What's the secret to the strength of you and Metabee?
글쎄요, 야생의 감이랄까?
I wonder. Could it be the instinct of wild!
뭐, 어쩌면, 가지고 태어난 재능이 넘쳐나는 것일지도!
It's possible that the gift we had is now overflowing!
완벽하게 번뜩이는 머리인 걸까요?
Could it be their brains shining bright?
아니, 제 엉망진창인 작전에 메타비가 꼭 응답해 줘요!
No, Metabee always responds to my plans in wreck!
무슨, 무슨! 잇키의 천재적인 아이디어에는 언제나 도움받아요.
Well, well! I always get helped by Ikki's genius ideas!
아니아니, 세계 2위가 된 건 메타비의 힘이 있어서에요!
No, no, we could become the two in the world, all thanks to Metabee's power!
무슨 소리야. 잇키의 작전 덕분이지!
What are you talking about? It's all thanks to your plans, Ikki!
아니아니, 네가!
No, no, it's all yours!
분명 일부러 아니꼽게 군다.
I'm sure that they're sickening us on purpose.
훌륭한 과잉 칭찬이야.
What an excellent backhanded compliment.
아, TV에 나가고 싶어!
I want to appear on TV!
그러니까, 둘의 조합이 최고의 결과를 낳는다는 것이네요?
You're saying the combination of you two is resulting in the best results!
맞아요! 메다로트와 메다로터는 일심동체!
Right! Medarot and Medarotter are one mind and one body!
단단한 신뢰의 정으로 맺어진 우정!
The friendship formed from firm compassion of trust!
그것이 승리의 열쇠에요!
That's the key to the victory!
-Complimenti! 대단해요!
-역시 세계 제 2위!
-Complimenti! Awesome!
-That's the 2nd in the world!
무슨, 무슨!
Well, well!
뭔 개소리야!
That makes no sense whatsoever!
누구?
Who was that?
방송중인데...
We're on air at the moment...
저기야!
Over there!
들어! 엉터리 메다로터 놈들! 신뢰? 우정? 그런 거 아무 역할도 안 해.
Listen to me, you quack Medarotter brats! Trust? Friendship? That does nothing at all.
필요한 건 힘! 적을 파괴하는 절대적인 힘이다!
What we need is power! The ultimate power to destroy an enemy!
-긴카이!
-엉터리?!
-Ginkai!
-Quack?!
그래, 찍어!
Right! Shoot it!
그래! 저 방법이라면 확실하게 나올 수 있었어! 왜 생각 못 했지?!
Right! That would have guaranteed me to get on TV! Why couldn't I think that?!
두목, 그런 문제가...
Boss, that's not the problem...
로보틀이다! 너희 그 콧대를 꺾어 놓아 주겠어! 전송!
We'll have a Robattle! I'll take you down a peg! Transfer!
NSJ형 넷세지
NSJ Type Nessage
큰일입니다! 잇키 군이 돌연 로보틀에 휘말렸습니다!
This is bad! Ikki is forced into a Robattle!
잇키 군...
Ikki...
이런 도발에 넘어가면 안 돼, 잇키!
You must not fall over to his provocation, Ikki!
그래, 그래, 다음에 보자.
Yeah, yeah, see you next time.
뭐, 뭐야?!
W- what?!
TV 생중계 중이야. 방해하지 마.
We're live on TV. Don't hinder.
도, 도망치냐! 전국 생중계에서 난 겁쟁이라고 선언하고 있잖아!
A- are you running away?! You're declaring that you're a coward in a live broadcast to all over the world!
도발해도 소용 없다니까! 진짜 메다로터는 그냥 싸우는 로보틀 따위는 안 해!
Again, there's no use of provocating me! A real Medarotter does not Robattle just to fight!
그래! 우리에게는 세계 제 2위의 자존심하고 책임이 있어!
Right! We have the pride and responsibility of the 2nd of the world!
뭐라고?! 시건방지게!
What?! How impertinent!
뭔 짓이야?!
What was that for?!
상대하지 않는다면 내 맘대로 부숴 주겠다!
If you're not going to face me, then I'll destroy him on my own!
이 자식!
You bastard!
잇키! 이 이상 못 참아!
Ikki! I can't stand this anymore!
-그래.
-때려눕혀 주겠어!
-Right.
-I'll knock him down!
좋아! 버추얼 아이!
Right! Virtual Eye!
힘내, 잇키!
Do your best, Ikki!
로보틀입니다! 로보틀이 시작되어 버렸습니다!
It's a Robattle! A Robattle has begun!
전 이대로 실황을 중계해 드리겠습니다!
I'll keep relaying the situation!
빨라!
How quick!
메타비!
Metabee!
헤! 어떠냐.
Heh! How was that?
이런 거, 몸풀기조차 안 되네!
That was too easy.
이 자식!
You bastard!
젠장!
Damn!
메타비의 연속 펀치! 역시 세계 대회 준우승! 대단한 힘입니다!
Metabee's continuous punch! That's the power of the 2nd of the world championship! What power!
Forza! 메타비, 힘내요!
Forza! Metabee, do your best!
기선 제압이 안 되는군!
Your stepping in is slow!
저런! 배틀 중에 파트를 교환했습니다! 이건 규칙 위반이 아닌가요?
Oh? He changed a part during the battle! Isn't this a violation of the rules?
규칙이 뭐! 싸우는 것의 목적은 이기는 거야! 이기기 위해서라면 뭐라도 할 수 있어! 그것이 진짜 싸움이야!
What about the rules? Fighting is for winning! I can do anything to win! That's the real fight!
아니야! 정정당당하게 싸우지 않으면 진짜 승부라고 할 수 없어!
No! If you don't fight fair and square, it isn't a real fight!
웃기지 마라!
Don't make me laugh!
메타비! 레클리스 모드야!
Metabee! To Reckless Mode!
좋아!
Right!
메타비, 변형! 이건 대단한 속도입니다!
Metabee has transformed! What speed he has!
메타비, 위기! 레클리스 모드에서는 방어 태세를 취할 수 없습니다!
Metabee's in crisis! He can't get into defensive position in Reckless Mode!
Attenzione! 조심해요!
Attenzione! Watch out!
뭐, 뭣이?!
W- what?!
저런! 메타비가 수영장에 떨어졌습니다!
No! Metabee has fallen into the pool!
메타비!
Metabee!
이, 이게! 놔!
Y- you bastard! Unhand me!
왜 그래, 메타비! 메타비!
What's wrong, Metabee? Metabee!
이상합니다. 메타비가 떠오르지 않습니다! 카메라 씨, 위로, 위로!
That's not right. Metabee's not getting up! Cameraman, up, up!
메타비!
Metabee!
젠장!
Damn!
늦어!
You're slow!
메타비.
Metabee.
이건...
That's...
메타비 기능 정지입니다! 승자, 넷세지! 세계 대회 준우승자 텐료 잇키 군과 메타비가 패배했습니다!
Metabee stopped functioning! Winner, Nessage!
World championship semi-finals winner, Tenryo Ikki and Metabee have lost!
대체 어떻게 된 일일까요? Mamma mia!
How could this be? Mamma mia!
우라가스미, 돌아가자.
Uragasumi, let's go back.
네, 도련님.
Understood, young master.
무슨. 잇키가... 메타비가 지다니...
How could this be? Ikki and Metabee have lost...
잇키야, 뭐가 정정당당이냐? 이기지 못하면 아무 의미도 없어.
Hey, Ikki, what's so great about being fair and square? There's no meaning in doing that if you can't win.
잠깐.
Wait.
1주 후.
A week later.
뭐라고?
What?
1주 후 다시 여기서 싸워!
Fight me here again after a week!
잇키.
Ikki.
상관 없어. 다시 창피당하고 싶으면 말이야.
I don't care, if you want to be embarrassed again.
리턴 매치 선언입니다! 잇키 군, 1주 후 리턴 매치를 선언했습니다!
It's a declaration of a return match! Ikki has declared a return match after a week!
막았는데, 내 말 안 들었잖아.
I stopped you, but you didn't listen to me.
어쩔 수 없었어. 일방적으로 걸어 왔으니까.
It couldn't be helped. They came to attack us one-handedly.
그래서 무슨 작전 있지?
So, you must have a plan, right?
어?
Huh?
리턴 매치를, 네가 직접 선언했으니까 뭔가 생각해 둔 거지?
You declared a return match by yourself, so you must have thought of something by now, right?
음, 아니, 그게 아직.
Well, no, not yet.
뭐라고?
What?
그렇게라도 말 안 하면 멋 안 나잖아! 일본 전국으로 중계되고 있었어!
It would be not cool to not declare that! We were being broadcast to all over Japan!
그래도...
But...
괜찮아! 이번엔 안 져.
Don't worry! We won't lose next time.
그래. 다시는 안 당할 거야!
Yeah. We won't lose ever again!
뭐야, 그게. 작전도 아무것도 없이 이길 리가 없잖아?
What's wrong with you? There's no way you'll win without a plan!
뭐야! 잘난 척...은...
What was that?! Don't try to... be...
너희들은 우리 메다로터의 대표잖아. 데스 메다로트에게 지는 꼴은 보고 싶지 않아!
Aren't you the representative of all us Medarotters? I don't want to see you guys being lost to Death Medarot!
뭐야, 쟤.
What's wrong with her?
분한 거야.
She's mortified.
나에 씨.
Ms. Nae.
아리카도 엄연한 메다로터야. 비겁한 데스 메다로트를 용서할 수 있을 리가 없어. 그러니까, 너희에게는 반드시 이겼으면 하는 거야.
Arika too is a good Medarotter. It's no way possible for her to forgive cowardly Death Medarots.
That's why she wants you guys to win, no matter what.
제일 분한 건 우리야!
We're the most mortified ones!
잇키 군.
Ikki.
긴카이 놈, 수중에서 한 대 더 숨겨 뒀어! 그래도, 그런 걸 핑계로 대고 싶지 않아!
That Ginkai bastard hid another one underwater! But I don't want to take that as an excuse of being lost!
놈들이 어떤 더러운 수를 쓰더라도, 정정당당하게 싸워 이길 거야! 그러지 않으면 의미가 없어.
No matter what kind of dirty trick they use, we will fight and win fair and square! Or, it would be meaningless.
우리는 우리 방식으로 이길 거야!
We will win, with our own ways!
그게 우리의 자존심이야!
That's our pride!
역시 긴카이 씨! 아기 손을 비트는 것과 같은 거네요!
That's Mr. Ginkai I knew! It's just like twisting a baby's hand!
당연하지.
Of course.
리턴 매치 때에는 불초 이 키쿠히메가 완벽하게 시중을 들어 드리겠습니다.
In a return match, I, Kikuhime, will help you no matter what.
어? 필요 없어, 그딴 거.
What? I don't need that.
그런 소리 마시고, 잇키하고 메타비에 대해서라면 다른 누구보다도 자세히 아니까.
Don't say that! I know best about Ikki and Metabee than anyone else.
흥, 시중을 들고 싶으면 잇키 놈들이 뭘 하는지 보고 와!
Hmph, if you want to help, then go find out what are Ikki and Metabee up to.
아, 네, 네!
Oh, right, right!
가자, 니들!
Let's go, you guys!
역시 두목! 강한 편에 붙는 게 TV에 나오는 횟수가 많으니까요.
That's our boss! Joining the stronger side will get you to be on the TV more often!
난입 작전은 안 해요?
Aren't we going to do intrusion plan?
못 이기면 꼴불견이잖아.
We'll be so unsightly if we can't win.
역시 대단해요, 두목!
I knew it, boss!
그런 소리는 했는데, 어떻게 해야 이기지?
Now I've said that, what should we do to win?
놈은 또 물 속으로 날 떨어뜨릴 생각이겠지.
They are going to drop me into water again.
우리도 물 위에서 이동할 수 있었다면...
If we also could move on the water...
부유 파트를 쓰는 건 절대 싫어! 난 이 동체로 놈들을 쓰러트릴 거야!
I will not use floating parts! I will take those bastards down with this body!
당연해! 어제하고 완전히 똑같은 조건으로 싸우지 않으면 의미가 없어!
Of course! If we don't fight in the exact same condition with yesterday, it's meaningless!
젠장!
Damn!
왜, 잇키?
What is it, Ikki?
이거야! 알아냈어!
This is it! I found it out!
뭘 하고 있을까요?
I wonder what they're doing.
그렇구나. 놈들 작전을 알겠어.
I see. I realized what their strategy is.
돌을 던진다고?
They're gonna throw rocks?
잇키 놈, 분명 긴카이 씨에게 돌을 던져서 조작을 방해할 생각이에요.
That Ikki will throw rocks to you and hinder your orderings.
어? 무슨 비겁한!
What? How cowardly!
그러나 이 작전에는 중대한 결점이 있습니다. 수영장 옆에 돌은 없습니다! 긴카이 씨가 이기는 건 확실해요.
But there is a major problem with this strategy. There are no rocks next to the pool! You're going to win, Mr. Ginkai.
그렇구나! 역시 두목! 머리 좋아!
I see! That's our boss! You're smart!
꺼져!
Get lost!
그딴 작전 쓸 리가 없잖아! 이 멍청아!
There is no way possible they would do that! You idiots!
대단한 바보들이다, 니들! 바보!
You are horribly stupid! Stupid, I say!
일주일 후라고 선언은 했는데, 그래서 어쩔 생각일까, 잇키 놈.
He declared that he'll have a match after a week, but what will Ikki do?
체육관? 이 시간에?
Gym? In a time like this?
뭐야, 이게?
What's this?
가자, 메타비!
Let's do this, Metabee!
좋아!
Right!
괜찮아?
Are you alright?
어, 이 공격은 임팩트의 순간이 제일 무방비지?
Well, doesn't this attack leaves me defenseless at the moment of impact?
그 순간을 알아내라고 한 건 너야.
It's you who told me to find out that moment.
미안, 조금만 더 밝으면 보기 편했을 텐데.
Sorry. It would be easier to see, if it was brighter.
어쩔 수 없지! 밤밖에 몰래 들어올 수 없기도 하고, 누구도 알면 안 되니까 말이야!
It can't be helped! We can sneak into here only at nights, and we can't let anyone know about this.
그렇지. 긴카이에게 밝혀지면 아무것도 안 돼!
That's right. If Ginkai finds out, then what we're doing will be in vain!
꼭 이길 거야!
We will win!
건전지 다 떨어졌네.
The batteries are out.
아직 할 수 있어! 다시 한번 와!
We can still do this! Come again!
좋아, 간다!
Alright! Here I go!
그래!
Right!
있잖아, 브라스.
Hey, Brass.
뭐야?
What is it?
제일 분한 건 잇키하고 메타비였을 거야.
Ikki and Metabee were the ones who were most mortified.
어? 무슨 말이야?
Huh? What are you talking about?
레클리스 모드!
Reckless Mode!
날아지질 않아. 몇 번을 해도.
You can't fly. We tried numerous times.
몇 번이라도 할 거야! 될 때까지!
I'll keep doing it until I make it!
리턴 매치는 내일이야! 이래선 못 이겨!
The return match is tomorrow! We can't win now!
잇키.
Ikki.
다른 작전도 생각 안 나. 이제 틀렸어.
I can't think of another plan. We're doomed.
그런 소리 마! 너는 분하지 않아? 진 채로?
Don't say that! Aren't you mortified? When we're lost?
분해! 분해도!
I am! I am mortified!
그럼 해! 안 된다고 말하기 전에 해!
Then do it! Before saying you can't do it, just do it!
메타비.
Metabee.
나는 아직 기능 정지되지 않았어. 아직 할 수 있어. 포기하면 거기서 끝이야.
I am still functional. I can still do it. If you give it up, then that's the end.
그래.
Right.
우리가 해줄 수 있는 건 아무것도 없어.
We can't do anything for them.
가자, 메타비!
Let's do this, Metabee!
아침이에요!
Mornin'!
자, 돌격! 아이들 쇼 특별 기획! 시청자 여러분이 직접 등장! 의 또다른 특별 기획!
The special project on Charge! Children's Show! Audience's Participation! And this is one more extra special project!
전국 메다로터가 주목하는 리턴 매치의 날이 왔습니다!
Today's the day of the return match, waited by all the Medarotters in the whole country!
세계 제 2위의 자존심을 걸고 텐료 잇키와 메타비 씨가 이웃 도부로크 신도시에서 덤벼온 긴카이 군의 넷시지하고 싸웁니다!
With the pride of being the 2nd in the world, Tenryo Ikki and Metabee is fighting
against Nessage of Ginkai who came from neighboring Doburoku new town!
안 돼, 안 돼!
No, no!
저, 저는 긴카이 군하고 친구에요!
Hey, I'm a friend of Ginkai!
방해방해!
You're interfering.
뭐야, 그 동체는. 하나도 안 바뀌었잖아!
What's wrong with that body? Nothing's changed!
메다로트의 힘은 파트에서 나오는 게 아니야!
The strength of a Medarot does not come from its parts!
흥! 부유 파트도 없이 이길 리가 없지!
Hmph! You aren't going to win without a floating part!
안 해 보면 몰라!
You won't know until you see!
뭔 작전을 생각해 왔는지는 모르겠지만 결과는 똑같다!
I don't know what you're up to, but the result is same!
자, 시작했습니다!
It begun!
Forza! 메타비!
Forza! Metabee!
그러니까, 그래선 이길 리가 없다니까?
I'm telling you that you aren't going to win at that rate!
이랴!
Take this!
같은 수 쓸 생각 마라. 의욕은 있냐?
Don't even think about trying the same thing. Are you even trying at all?
메타비! 레클리스 모드야!
Metabee! To Reckless Mode!
좋아!
Right!
흥.
Hmph.
뭐야?!
What?!
어떠냐!
How was that?!
Bravo! 훌륭해요!
Bravo! So excellent!
대단해요! 메타비가 수면에서 뛰었습니다!
It's awesome! Metabee has jumped off the water surface!
꽤나 머리 썼구나.
So you did have a plan.
머, 먹어라!
T- take this!
기다렸다!
I've been waiting!
좋아, 그대로 계속해!
Great! Keep doing like that!
에잇, 코쿠류는 뭘 하고 있는 거야?!
Damn, what is Kokuryu doing?!
그렇구나. 이래서는 너무 빨라서 못 잡아.
I see. Now he's too fast to catch.
그래도 그 정도로 이길 수 있을 거라는 생각은 마.
But don't think that you can win by that.
돌격 유닛 전송!
Charge Unit, transfer!
넷세지를 위에서 대기시키라고? 좋아, 두고 봐라!
Place Nessage on air and wait? Alright, this must work!
여기까지 와 봐라, 엉터리야!
Try coming to here, you junk!
어딜 가냐!
You aren't going anywhere!
왜 그래, 메타비?!
What's wrong, Metabee?!
전에 그 놈이야. 수중에서 공격해오고 있어!
It's the guy from the last time. It's attacking from inside the water!
뭐라고?!
What?!
젠장! 수면에서 뛰는 순간을 노리고 있는 한 레클리스 모드로는 아무것도 못 해!
Damn! If it's aiming for the moment for him to jump on the water surface, Reckless Mode won't get him anywhere!
-메타비, 위험해!
-지면 안 돼!
-Metabee, watch out!
-Don't lose!
젠장! 이걸 어째야!
Damn! What should we do?!
메타비!
Metabee!
뭐라고? 그런 게 될 리가...
What?! That isn't going to work...
괜찮아. 돼.
Don't worry. It will.
떨어지면 끝이다.
If I fall, then I'm going down.
길게 생각하지 말고 일단 해 봐. 넌 아직 기능 정지 상태가 아니야. 너라면 할 수 있어!
There is no time to evaluate this plan, so just go do it. You are still functional. It's possible because it's you!
포기하면 거기서 끝이야!
If you give up, then it's the end!
그래, 그랬지.
Yes, you're right.
왜 그래, 엉터리 메타비 씨?
What's wrong, Mr. Junk Metabee?
난 엉터리가 아니랬다!
I am not a junk!
멍청하긴.
How foolish.
이게!
You bastard!
말도 안 돼.
No way.
해냈구나, 메타비!
You did it, Metabee!
넷세지, 기능 정지! 메타비가 이겼습니다!
Nessage stopped functioning! Metabee wins!
Bravo! 메타비!
Bravo! Metabee!
-해냈어!
-메타비가 이겼어!
-They did it!
-Metabee won!
봤냐! 이게 메다로트의 힘이야! 이게 진짜 승리야!
Did you see that?! This is the power of Medarot! This is the true victory!
돌아가자, 우라가스미.
Let's go back, Uragasumi.
해냈구나, 잇키! 난 널 믿었어!
전 잇키하고 친구로...
You did it, Ikki! I believed in you!
I'm Ikki's friend...
안 돼, 안 돼!
No, no!
날뛰게 해 줄게, 유니트리스.
I'll let you rage, Unitrix.
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
잇키하고 친구들은 배터리가 얼마 안 남은 메타비하고 같이 해수욕을 즐기고 있었다.
Ikki and his friends were enjoying swimming at the sea, when Metabee's battery level was low.
한편 코쿠류는 최강의 데스 메다로트 유니트리스하고 엑사이즈를 손에 넣는다.
Meanwhile, Kokuryu obtains the strongest Death Medarots: Unitrix and Excise.
실력을 연습하러 온 긴카이의 유니트리스가 메타비에게 덤빈다.
Ginkai took Unitrix with him to challenge Metabee and test his abilities.
메타비의 배터리 잔량이 0에 다가가며, 버추얼 아이가 사라졌다.
When Metabee's battery level reaches zero, his Virtual Eye disappeared.
메타비의 행방은 어찌 되는가?
What's going to happen to Metabee?
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 전사의 정: 전편
Next time on Medarot Damashii! Compassion of Warriors: Part 1
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!